David A. Kleinberg

362 Concord Street Holliston, MA 01746 | (508) 847-3606 | davidkleinberg@jhu.edu LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/david-kleinberg Website: dkleinberg.wixsite.com/mysite

Skills Summary

Software: Highly knowledgeable in programming with Java, C, C++, JavaFX, Unit Testing Frameworks, and writing Checkstyle compliant code. Experienced in Matlab, Swift, Xcode SDK, JavaScript, CSS & HTML.

Hardware: Well versed in Fabrication, 3D Printing, Computer-Aided Design (CAD), Circuit Analysis, and lab work with Oscilloscopes. **Applications:** Proficient in data acquisition with LabVIEW and Microsoft Excel. Technical skills in data analysis for natural sciences. **Languages:** Fluent in Spanish and well-versed in Hebrew.

Education

Johns Hopkins University, Class of 2019

GPA: 3.14

Bachelor of Science in Electrical Engineering

Classes

Electrical Engineering: Digital Systems Fundamentals; Signals & Systems; Circuits; Field, Matter & Waves; Physics I & II with Labs Computer Science: Intermediate Programming in C & C++; Data Structures https://github.com/DavidKleinberg/DataStructures Math: Calculus (through Multivariable); Linear Algebra; Differential Equations

Engineering Projects & Experience

Stock Investment Program Design, August 2016 – Present

Programmed algorithms (in Java) to map stock trends. Refactored code for maintainability based on academic coursework. Goal: utilize the E*TRADE API to run autonomous investing.

Go-Kart Project, March – June 2015

Designed, machined, and assembled a Go-Kart. Compiled portfolio of documented design process, budget, and engineering calculations. Blog posts with updates and progress reports can be found at: https://maavar2015.wordpress.com/

Work Experience

President of TAMID at Johns Hopkins University, October 2015 – Present

Project Leader for Say2Eat Consulting, Recruitment Director for JHU Chapter, Business Consultant for Welltika

Winner of national competition: Recipient of monetary award for "Best Market Research Deliverable" and featured on Tamid Nationals' website for outstanding Project Manager.

Intern at Clarity Advisors, May 2016 – September 2016

Consultant for Hypertunity

Launched US operations. Developed collaterals, website, and other marketing strategies. Led a web campaign using MailChimp. Evaluated product messages with CEO. Helped build and promote Hypertunity's operations and on-line presence.

Tufts Health Plan (Paid Summer Internships), June 2013 - August 2014

Commercial Claims Operations – Summer 2014

Handled confidential client information while working on company database. Performed claims processing functions on over 5,000 beneficiaries.

Real Estate Department – Summer 2013

Constructed outdoor health and wellness center and assembled cubicles and desk spaces.

Received an honorable mention in internal corporate newsletter for distinguished summer intern.

Leadership Contributions

FTC Robotics, Gann Academy

Mentor - Present

Develop game strategy and project management. Analyze design with concepts in mechanical physics and CAD software.

Head of Hardware & Design − 2014 and 2015

Led workshops in building techniques and design strategy (using CAD). Created robot for FTC competition. Implemented 3D printing to prototyping and small assemblies. Mentored underclassmen.

Gann Academy MakerSpace, March 2015

Founder

Received funding of nearly \$10,000 for the purchase of a 3D printer and won two printers from FIRST competition. Initiated and implemented a culture of technology and innovation in both the school's art and science departments.